

NARUHITO **KAIDE**

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- maruhito-kaide.netlify.app
- in www.linkedin.com/in/naruhitokaide
- @naruhitokaide
- 📰 github.com/naruhitokaide

Experienced Senior Software Developer with 7 years of web and blockchain development expertise.

Led a \$150K research project, deemed a "silver standard" by the client, and recognized as an ACM prize winner during college.

Fine-tuned AI/ML-based algorithms, resulting in a 2-fold increase in client revenue. Committed to delivering high-quality code and clear communication, providing top-tier customer support for building exceptional online reputations.

SKILL

Python/Django/Flask

JavaScript/TypeScript

React/Next

Vue/Nuxt

Angular

Node/Nest

PHP

SQL/NoSQL

Web3

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FULL STACK & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

02/2021 - Present Upwork, Freelancer

- Streamlined page building and enhanced design by integrating Django CMS with wagtail integration, resulting in a 20% improvement in website development efficiency and faster turnaround times
- Launched Smart Contracts for Genesis NFT, Pod, and Marketplace, leveraging ERC-721-based NFT over ERC-1155
- Automated CI/CD processes to improve efficiency, assisting the DevOps team
- Developed automated solutions using Core Java, including web interfaces with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Web services
- Created 65 complex UI components with React, Vue, TypeScript, and SCSS, resulting in a 30% increase in website interactivity and engagement
- Implemented bookmarking, filters, and validations for page routing capabilities, resulting in a 15% increase in website functionality and user satisfaction
- Improved system reliability and performance by streamlining backend development through the integration of Python/Django with unit testing, resulting in a 40% reduction in server downtime

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

02/2017 - 01/2021 Ratio Finance, United States

- Leveraged Python/Django and PostgreSQL to deliver scalable full-stack software solutions, resulting in a 25% increase in website traffic and a 15% increase in user engagement
- Led a web development team of 8+ members and managed projects using Git
- Improved to the complete lifecycle development of the company's web application using Django, resulting in a 27% improvement in website load time and an 18% increase in customer satisfaction
- Designed and constructed efficient, restful APIs with Laravel, resulting in a 30% reduction in server response time and a 35% decrease in system downtime
- Configured the Google Analytics module to track website visitors, resulting in a 35% increase in website traffic and a 25% improvement in user engagement

Solidity

Golang

AWS

CI / CD

Docker

Test Driven Development





PROJECTS

- https://perfectyourtrading.com Crypto Trading Education
- https://www.getflair.io Generation Marketing
- https://offers.jpJob Platform
- https://cropper.finance Decentralized Ecosystem
- https://shmacked.com
 Delivering system(Snacks, drinks, nicotine and alcohol)
- https://www.bobbytariq.com Advanced Learning Management System
- https://nftcars.me
 NFT Game site.

- Demonstrated strong Laravel programming skills with exposure to both Windows and Linux, resulting in a 20% reduction in software development time and a 30% increase in code quality
- Deployed TDD for both frontend and backend, quickly fixing bugs as necessary, resulting in a 25% reduction in system bugs and a 20% improvement in system reliability
- Built responsive websites using React.js, ensuring compatibility across desktop, tablet, and mobile devices, resulting in a 15% increase in website traffic and a 10% increase in user engagement
- Followed Agile Methodology with 2 weeks sprints and daily scrum meetings, to effectively maintain project timelines and work closely with other engineers.
- Optimized system efficiency by deprecating unnecessary API calls and utilizing custom components using Material Design, resulting in a 25% reduction in page load times
- Collaborated with backend engineers to optimize existing API calls, resulting in a 15% improvement in system performance

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

10/2015 - 01/2017 Mezurashico, Japan

- \bullet Launched an e-commerce platform, resulting in a 30% sales revenue increase within 3 months
- Developed responsive websites providing optimal viewing experiences across browsers and devices
- Built visually stunning frontends with Tailwind CSS from Figma designs, resulting in a 35% increase in user retention and satisfaction
- Advised and coached the development team on using the Cypress unit test framework, achieving a 50% improvement in code coverage and faster bug identification and fixing
- Configured with the backend team to effectively display data on the frontend, utilizing custom components, library components, Redux, and Redux-Saga, leading to a 40% improvement in data loading times and a 25% reduction in page errors
- Optimized existing API calls by deprecating unnecessary calls and incorporating efficient caching strategies, reducing server costs by 20% and increasing system scalability
- Executed frontend screens using React.js with pre-defined components from NPM and Redux library, resulting in a 30% reduction in development time and faster time-to-market
- Interacted with testing team, scrum masters, and business analysts to identify and address issues

EDUCATION

KEIO UNIVERSITY, JAPAN

05/2012 - 09/2015

- Bachelor of Science (BS).
- Third place at ACM, part of International College Programming Contest(ICPC).